Sam Gejdenson Papers 2001.0008
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: An Inventory, undated, 1966-2001
  - Press Releases, undated, 1985-1987 (Box 68)
    - National Politics, undated, 1986
    - Budget Reactions, 1988 February 18
    - Campaign Literature, undated, 1986
    - Post-Election, undated, 1985-1988
    - Town Meetings, 1987 March 2
    - Double Water Subsidies, 1987 March 5
    - Handicapped Parking, 1987 March 18
    - Gejdenson Names Staff, 1987 April 21
    - Home Base Business, 1987 April 9
    - Statement on Soviet Exchange, 1987 April 22
    - Nuclear Reglator Commission (NRC) Inspector General, 1987 April 23
    - Diversification, 1987 May 4
    - McKinney Statement, 1987 May 4
    - Restore Sales Tax Reduction, 1987 September 16
  - Foreign Affairs, undated, 1978-1992 (Box 69)
    - Russia, 1991-1992
    - Gejdenson's Opinions, 1988
    - Saudi Arms Sales, F-18, 1992
    - USSR, 1989-1992
    - U.S./Soviet Joint Venture, 1990
    - Chernobyl Research, 1991-1992
    - Sri Lanka, 1991-1992
    - Syria, 1990-1992
    - Terrorism, 1988-1991
    - Togo, 1988-1990
    - United Arab Emirates, 1991
    - Ukraine, 1982, 1991
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1989-1991
    - United Nations, 1988-1991
    - Volunteer Organizations, 1988-1991
    - War Powers, 1987-1988
    - Zaire, 1991
    - Saudi Arabia, 1978-1991
    - South Africa, 1989-1991
    - South Africa Sanctions, 1989-1990
    - Soviet Jews, 1989-1991
    - Chernobyl Amendements, undated
    - FSA: Center for International Studies (CIS) Aid Pack, 1992
    - Sudan, 1988-1989
    - Taiwan, 1990
    - Tibet, 1988-1991
    - Turkey, 1991
    - Ukraine, "Children of Chernobyl", 1990-1991
    - United Nations Population Fund (UNPFA), 1989-1991
    - Visa Information, 1991
    - Yugoslavia, 1991-1992
    - Zimbabwe, 1990
  - Press Clippings, undated,1995-1996 (Box 70)
    - Mashantucket Pequots, undated, 1995-1996
    - Medicare, undated, 1995-1996
    - Medicaid, undated, 1995-1996
    - General, undated, 1995-1996
    - Mohegans, undated, 1996
    - Letters to the Editor, undated, 1996
    - Local Issues, undated, 1995-1996
    - Op/Eds, undated, 1995-1996
    - Nuclear, undated, 1995-1996
    - Naval Undersea Warfare Center/Naval Undersea Systems Center (NUWC/NUSC), undated, 1995-1996
    - Pratt & Whitney, undated, 1995-1996
    - John Rowland, undated, 1995-1996
    - Gejdenson Clips, u 1996
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1992-1996 (Box 71)
    - General, undated, 1996
    - Agriculture, undated, 1995-1996
    - Banking, undated, 1995-1996
    - Base Closing, undated, 1995-1996
    - Budget, undated, 1995-1996
    - Business, undated, 1995-1996
    - Defense, undated, 1995-1996
    - Campaign Finance, undated, 1994-1996
    - Economy, undated, 1992-1996
    - Education, undated, 1995-1996
    - Electric Boat, undated, 1995-1996
    - Environment, undated, 1995-1996
    - Gambling, undated, 1996
    - Health Care, undated, 1995-1996
    - Housing, undated, 1996
    - Labor, undated, 1995-1996
    - Local Politics, undated, 1995-1996
    - Local Interests, undated, 1996
    - Local Events, undated, 1996
  - Press Clippings, undated, 1996-1998 (Box 72)
    - Transportation, undated, 1996-1998
    - Groton, undated, 1997-1998
    - Congressional Issues, undated, 1997-1998
    - Killingly, undated, 1996-1998
    - Lebanon, undated, 1997-1998
    - Ledyard, undated, 1997-1998
    - Lisbon, undated, 1997-1998
    - Lyme, undated, 1997-1998
    - Mansfield, undated, 1997-1998
    - Middletown, undated, 1996-1998
    - Montville, undated, 1997-1998
    - North Stonington, undated, 1996-1998
    - Norwich, undated, 1997-1998
    - Old Lyme, undated, 1997-1998
    - Old Saybrook, undated, 1997
    - Preston, undated, 1997-1998
    - Putnam, undated, 1997-1998
    - Salem, undated, 1997-1998
    - Scotland, undated, 1997-1998
    - Stamford, undated, 1997-1998
    - Sterling, undated, 1997-1998
    - Stonington, undated, 1997-1998
    - Mystic, undated, 1997-1998
    - Tolland, undated, 1997
    - Vernon, undated, 1997-1998
    - Voluntown, undated, 1997-1998
    - Waterford, undated, 1997-1998
    - Westbrook, undated, 1997-1998
    - Willington, undated, 1997-1998
    - Windham, undated, 1996-1998
    - Woodstock, undated, 1997-1998
  - Impeachment, undated, 1974-1998 (Box 73)
    - Communication from Kenneth Starr, 1998 September 11
    - Scholarly Material on Impeachment, undated, 1974, 1998
    - Article on Nixon Impeachment, 1974
    - Impeachment in the 1980s, 1986-1989
    - Legal Materials, 1998
    - House of Representatives' Resolutions, 1998
    - President's Rebuttal and Statement, 1998
    - Dear Colleague Letters and Lieberman's Statement, 1998
    - Press with Gejdenson in them, undated, 1998
    - Gejdenson's Statement, 1998
    - Prior to Impeachment Press, undated, 1998
    - Press following Impeachment Vote, undated, 1998
    - Materials from Democratic Leadership, 1998 September
    - Resolutions to Impeach from Starr, 1998 October
    - Committee Reports and Statements, 1998 December
    - Starr Testimony and Report, 1998 November 19
    - 51 Questions, undated, 1998
    - Submission by the President's Council, 1998 December 8-9
    - Gejdenson's Floor Statement, 1998 December 19
    - SK Notes and Background Analysis, 1998 November
    - Censure Resolution, 1998
    - Organizations' Opinions on Impeachment, 1998 December
    - Censure Press Clippings, 1998 December 13
  - Question Period Legislation, Correspondence, General Legislation, Bulk, 1983-2000; undated, 1943, 1983-2000 (Box 74)
    - Rules of the House of Representatives, undated
    - Rules Study, 1985-1991
    - General Background on Question Period, undated, 1943, 1991
    - Testimony, 1992 March 18
    - Talking Points, undated
    - House Resolution 155, 1991 May 16
    - Hearings, 1991-1992
    - Floor Statement, 1991 May
    - Responses, 1991-1992
    - Dear Colleague Letters, 1991
    - General Correspondence, undated
    - Final Draft of Legislation, 1991-1992
    - Press on Question Period, undated, 1991-1992
    - Draft Legislation, 1991
    - For Approval, 1991
    - Jewish Related Activities, 1983
    - Tahnk You letters, Congratulation Letters, etc., 1983, 1985
    - Thank You Letters to Gejdenson, 1983
    - Letters to Gejdenson, 1983
    - Holiday Cards, 1983
    - Thank You Letters From Gejdenson, 1983
    - House Resolution 4199, 1999
    - House Resolution 3313, 1999-2000
    - House Resolution 574, 1999
    - House Resolution 983, 1999
    - House Resolution 983, 1999
    - House Resolution 2900, 1999-2000
    - House Resolution 525, 1999
    - House Resolution 960, 1999
    - House Resolution 1234, 2000
    - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge (ANWR), 1999
    - House Resolution 1350, 1999
    - House Resolution 1401, 1999
    - House Resolution 1372, 1999
    - House Resolution 1549, 1999
    - House Resolution 1581, 1999
    - House Resolution 1619, 1999
    - House Resolution 1674, 1999
    - House Resolution 1734, 2000
    - House Resolution 1775, 1999
    - House Resolution 4249, 1999
    - House Resolution 3032, 1999-2000
    - House Resolution 4794, 2000
    - House Resolution 3379, 2000
    - Plum Island, 1999-2000
    - American Heritage River, 1999
    - American Heritage River Initiative, 1997
    - Flounder Quota, 1996
    - Heritage Corridor, 1996-1997
    - National Oceanographic Partnership Pact, 1996-1997
    - Poquentanuck Cove, 1996
    - Rhode Island Oil Spill, 1996
  - Defense Files, undated, 1989-1997 (Box 75)
    - Submarine Press, 1994-1996
    - Kildare Corporation (PADS), 1994-1997
    - Rideshare Program, Naval Undersea Warfare Center (NUWC), 1989-1996
    - Naval Undersea Warfare Center (NUWC) Closure and Reuse, 1995-1996
    - National Maritime Technology Center, 1994-1995
    - Naval Undersea Warfare Center (NUWC) Press, undated, 1995-1997
    - Civilian Personal Center, 1996
    - Connecticut, Gas Turbine Engine, 1995
    - National Guard, 1994-1996
    - Gilman Corportation, 1996
    - Environment Scholarship, 1995-1996
    - CVI Laser Information, 1996
    - Department of Defense, 1994-1996
    - C-17 Information, 1994-1995
    - Shipbuilding Caucus, 1995
    - Army Reserves, 76 Division, 1995
    - NAS Hunter Hearings, 1995-1996
    - SEATech, 1993-1996
    - Pratt & Whitney, 1992-1993
  - Nuclear Energy, undated, 1985-1991 (Box 76)
    - Nuclear Energy Book, 1991
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1990-1991
    - Millstone Corespondence, undated
    - Government Reports, Nuclear Regulatory Commission, NRC, 1986-1990
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, Coziness with Industry, 1987 December
    - Millstone III Pipe Break, 1991
    - Design Basis Threat Rulemaking, 1990-1991
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission Violations, 1989-1991
    - Millstone II Radiation, 1990
    - Millstone, NRC Investigation, 1989, 1991
    - Talking Points, American Nuclear Energy Council, undated
    - Report to Congress, Department of Energy and Nuclear Reglatory Commission, 1989-1991
    - Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, 1989-1990
    - Reports, 1989-1990
    - House Resolution 1549, Nuclear Regelatory Commission (NRC) reauthorization, 1989
    - House Resolution 1549, Decommissioning of Shoreham, 1989
    - Nuclear Reglatory Commission Press, undated, 1990
    - Seabrook, 1989-1990
    - Hearings- Inspector and Auditor, 1989
    - Gejdenson's Amendment to House Resolution 1711, 1985
    - "Nuclear Waste: Is There a Need for Interior Federal Storage?", 1989 November 1
    - The Nuclear Monitor, 1989-1991
  - Environment, Bulk, 1982-1997; undated, 1959, 1982-1997 (Box 77)
    - Connecticut Flounder Quota, 1992-1994
    - Long Island Sound, Coastal Zone Management, 1991, 1997
    - Connecticut Coastal Resources, 1992
    - Long Island Sound, Connecticut, 1988-1992
    - CISS Final Management Plan, 1994-1996
    - Coastal Zone Management and Reauthorization, 1995
    - Connecticut Spill Liability, 1989-1990
    - Marina Fees, 1989, 1993-1995
    - 104th Congress, 1994-1995
    - Connecticut Shellfish, 1989-1992
    - French River, Bulk, 1993-1994; 1959, 1993-1994
    - Superfund Revere Textile, 1986-1991
    - Eastern Conncticut Sludge Study, 1993
    - Flow Control, 1993-1996
    - Tanks, 1993
    - Livermaster Switch, 1993
    - MSW Incinerator Emissions, 1994 September 1
    - Ocean Dumping, 1986-1992
    - Illegal Dumping, 1989-1991
    - Canterbury Incinerator, 1992
    - Haddam Incinerator, 1990
    - Lisbon Incinerator, 1991-1995
    - Yaworki, 1982-1995
    - Killingly Wood Burning, 1988-1992
  - Bills and Correspondence, Oil, undated, 1995-2000 (Box 78)
    - Senior Bills, 1998-1999
    - Firefighter Bill, 1999
    - Bills and Correspondence, 1999
    - Campaign Finance Bill, 1999
    - Banking Bill, 1999
    - Tax Bills, 1998-1999
    - Pension Bills, 1999
    - Social Security Bill, 1998-1999
    - CAFE, Vichcle Efficency, 1998-2000
    - Oil Letters to Refiners, 2000
    - Diesel Fuel Standards, 2000
    - Democratic Leadership, 1999-2000
    - Taxes, 2000
    - Administration, 1998-2000
    - Hess Terminal, Groton, 2000
    - Low Income Weatherization Assistance Program, 2000
    - Natural Gas, Supply and Price, 2000
    - Fuel Oil, Price Spike, 2000
    - Energy Information Admistration, EIA, 2000
    - Oil Exports, 1999-2000
    - Roundtable, Oil and Gas, 2000
    - Letter to Lott, 2000
    - House Resolution 3822, Oil Price Reduction Act, 2000
    - Northeast Heating Oil Rescue Legislation, 2000
    - Gejdenson's Floor Amendment, 2000
    - IR Heating Oil Hearing, 2000
    - Gejdenson's Stategic Petroleum Reserves Resolution, 2000
    - Gejdenson's Letter and Release of Heating Oil, 2000
    - Fuel Prices, 1999-2000
    - Shoretel Project, 2000
    - Home Heating Oil, 1995-1997
    - Energy Star, 1998-2000
    - CRT, Weatherization Grant, 1999-2000
    - Public Power, 1997
    - Connecticut Municipal Electric Energy Corporation, 1995-2000
  - Press Cippings, Press Releases, Mailings, undated, 1996-2000 (Box 79)
    - Editorials, 1999-2000
    - Media Advisories, 1999-2000
    - Newletters, 1998-2000
    - Press Releases, 1999-2000
    - Windham Mill, 1999
    - Plum Island, 1999-2000
    - Lobsters, 1999-2000
    - International Relations, Ranking Member, 1998
    - Scorecards, 1998-2000
    - India n Trade Trip, 1999-2000
    - Connecticut Exports, 1998-2000
    - Silver Star, 1999
    - General Dynamics, Newport News Acquisition, 1999
    - Exports, Gejdenson's Bill, 1999
    - E-commerce, 1999
    - COPS Program, 1999
    - Coast Guard Museum, 1999-2000
    - After-School-Care Program Report, 1999
    - Cereal Report, 1996-1997
    - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), 1998
    - Connecticut River, undated
    - Africa n Trade Bill, 1999
    - Tariff Issue, 1999
    - Crane Letters, 1999
    - Baley Letters, 1999
    - Fabric Tariff, 1998-1999
    - Women, 1999
  - Tourism, Women's Issues, Admistrative Issues, undated, 1997-2000 (Box 80)
    - Tourism Conference, 2000
    - Tourism, Connecticut Data, 1997-2000
    - The Academy for Educational Development, 2000
    - Stenberg v. Carhart Decision, 2000
    - Abortion Literature, undated
    - Thank You Letters, 1998-2000
    - Staff Identification Card Applications, undated
    - Choice Votes, 1999-2000
    - Vernon, 1999
    - Mystic Tourism Reports, 1997
    - Planned Parenthood, NARA I, 2000
    - International Family Planning, 2000
    - Fair Pay Act, 2000
  - Native American Issues, undated, 1989-2000 (Box 81)
    - Washington D.C. Meeting Press, 2000 August 8-9
    - Freedom of Information Act, Eastern Pequots, 1999-2000
    - Proposed Funding for Recognition, 1998-2000
    - Technical Reports, 2000 February 14
    - Eastern Pequots, 1991-2000
    - Proposed Finding Summary, Charts, undated
    - Town Corespondence following proposed Finding, 2000
    - Ag Letters to Connecticut Delegation, 2000
    - Grover Memo on Recognition Proposal, 2000
    - Eastern Pequots, Town Meetings Requested, Press, 2000
    - Eastern Pequot Recognition Proposal, 2000
    - Eastern Pequots, Historial Material, 1991-1992
    - Golden Hill, Proposed Finding, 1998-2000
    - Golden Hill, Final Determination, 1999
    - Golden Hill Paugassetts, 1992-2000
    - Mohegans and Pequots, 1995
    - Mohegan Recognition Material, 1994
    - Mohegan, BAR, 1989-1993
    - Wiquapaug Pequots, undated
    - Waterbury/Paugassetts Argument, undated
    - Mohegan Tribal Nation, 1994
    - Nipmucs Recongition, 2000
  - Environmental Issues, undated, 1992-2000 (Box 82)
    - Lobsters, Long Island Sound, 2000
    - Government Reports, 1999-2000
    - Long Island Sound, 1997-2000
    - Environmental Protection, 1996-1998
    - Environment Memos, 1996
    - Environment, Tourism, and Women's Issues Press, 1999-200
    - Ground Fish Suspension, 1992-1995
    - Scallop Issues, 1998-1999
    - Fisheries, 1997-1998
    - Dredging Project, 1996-1997
    - University of Connecticut's Landfill, 1999
    - Essex, USA's Number One Small Town, 1995
    - Yaworski Landfill Site, 1999-2000
  - Native American Issues, Annexation, undated, 1983-1999 (Box 83)
    - Press Clippings, undated, 1993-1994
    - Agreement Proposal, undated, 1994
    - Final Trust Decision, 1995
    - Requests from Department of Interior Investigation, 1996
    - Court Proceedings, 1996
    - Judiciary, Native Americans, 1991-1993
    - Conflict Managment Group, 1994
    - Correspondence, Rescine, 1993-1995
    - Annexation, 1993-1996
    - Letters on Annexation Returned, 1993
    - Native American Funds, 1983
    - Mashantuckets, 1998-1999
    - Pequots, 1998
    - Memoranda, 1991-1993
    - Mashantucket Pequots, Trust, 1996-1997
    - Mashantucket Pequots, New Trust Application, 1999
    - Pequots and Town Negotiations, 1994
    - Simonds Family, 1995-1996
    - Ledyard Indian Zoning, 1992
    - Pequots/Ledyard, General Issues, 1999
    - Land Grant Issues, 1999
    - CTVS Babbit, 1999
    - Land in Trust Application, 1995-2000
    - Facilitation, 1992-1995
    - Casino Impact Study, 1991
    - Sovereignty Report, 1993-1994
    - Pequot/Town Disputes, 1993-1994
  - Animal Rights Issues, Children's Issues, Welfare, undated, 1989-2000 (Box 84)
    - Hurricane Prepardiness, 1996
    - Animal and Plant Health Inspection Service, APHIS, 1995
    - Animal Rights, 1995-1996
    - Canadian Seal Hunt, 1998-1999
    - 11 Chimps, 1995
    - Holloman Airforce Chimps, 1998
    - Deer Huunt: Bluff Point, 1996-1997
    - Deer Hunt, Groton, 1998-1999
    - Fur, 1995-1996
    - Steel Traps, 1999
    - Amistad, 1998-2000
    - Jason Foundation, 2000
    - Challenge Grants, 1997-1998
    - Mystic Seaport, 1998-2000
    - Intercountry Adoption Act, 2000
    - Healthy Meals for Children Act, 1997
    - Project Lift, 1999
    - Hunger in Connecticut, 1999-2000
    - Fork Act, 2000
    - Food Stamps, 1997-1998
    - Welfare in Connecticut, 1989-1997
    - Welfare Conference, 1996
    - Signed Letters, 1994-1996
    - School Nutrition, 1999-2000
    - Food Stamps, 1997
    - School Lunches, 1993-1995
    - Daycare Feeding, 1995
    - Easy Filling Bill, 1994
    - Substance Abuse, 1995-1996
    - Welfare Reform, 1996-1999
    - Millenium, 1995-1996
    - Welfare-to-Work Program, 1994-1995
    - Connecticut Work Grants, 1998-1999
    - Women's Center, 1999
    - El Cenito, 1999-2000
    - Immigration, 1997-1998
    - Crossfire, Lumber, 1996
  - Environment, undated, 1997-2000 (Box 85)
    - Environmental Outreach, 2000
    - Appropriations Request, Environment, 2000
    - Grants, 1997-2000
    - Bureau of Land Management ( BLM) and Forest Service, 2000
    - Baltic Mill Fire, 1999
    - Brownfields, 1998-1999
    - House Resolution 855, Dredging Long Island Sound, 1998-2000
    - American Heritage River Initative, 1997-2000
    - Fish Quotas, 1998-2000
    - Federal Emergancy Managment Acency ( FEMA), 2000
    - Japaness Whaling, 2000
    - League of Conservation Voters, 2000
    - Fisheries, 1998-2000
  - Press Releases and Press Clippings, Legislation, undated, 1993-2000 (Box 86)
    - Firefighter's Bill, 1999
    - Cops in School Grant, 1999
    - Press Realeases, 1997-1998
    - Education, 1998-1999
    - East Coast Greenway, 1999
    - Op/Eds, Columns, undated, 1998-1999
    - State of the Union, 1999
    - Gejdenson's Campaigns, 1997-2000
    - Social Security, 1999
    - Juvenile Justice/Gun Control, undated, 1999
    - Newletters, Periodicals, 1997-1999
    - Pensions, undated, 1998-1999
    - Health Maintance Oragnizations (HMOs), undated, 1998-1999
    - Press Clips, undated, 1993-1999
    - Radio Scripts, undated, 1999
    - Campaign Finance Reform, undated, 1999
    - Medicare and HMOs, undated, 1998
    - Internal Office Communication, 1996
  - Press Clippings, Correspondence, and Legislative Records, undated, 1996-1999 (Box 87)
    - Press Clippings, undated, 1996-1999
    - Postage Stamps, undated
    - The President's Summit for America's Future, undated
    - Election Investigation Research, 1997-1998
    - Submarines/Groton, undated, 1997-1998
    - Election Press and Manuals, undated, 1996-1998
    - Foreign Policy, 1997
    - Nuclear Power, Millstone, 1998-1999
    - Businesses and Small Businesses, undated, 1997-1998
    - Native Americans, undated, 1997-1998
    - National Issues, 1998
    - Campaign Press, undated, 1997-1998
    - Report to Congress: Heritage Corridor, 1999
    - Environment, undated, 1997-1998
    - Public Relations and Correspondence, 1997-1998
    - Outreach Groups, 1997-1998
    - Heritage River, 1997
    - Organization of Women Leaders (OWL), 1998
    - General Press, 1997-1998
  - Agriculture, undated, 1993-2000 (Box 88)
    - General Appropriations, 2000
    - Fiscal Year 2001, Agricultural Apprioriations, 2000
    - Fiscal Years 1999 and 2000, Appropriations, 1998-1999
    - Conncticut Dairy Facts, 1999-2000
    - Connecticut Drought, 1999
    - House Resolution 1604, Dairy Consumer and Producer Protection Act, 1999-2000
    - General Files, 1999
    - House Resolution 1402 Option 1-A, 1999-2000
    - House Resolution 1402 Amendments, 1999-2000
    - Food Marketing, 1993, 1999
    - Perserving Conncticut Farmland, 2000
    - Farm Credit, 1998
    - University of Connecticut, 1998-2000
    - Oragnic Food, 1997-1998
    - New England R,C, and D Council, 1999-2000
    - Agricultural Grants, 1999-2000
    - West Nile Information, 1999-2000
    - Farm Bureau Federation Investigation, 2000
    - Affects of Kyoto on Agriculture, 1999
    - Agriculture, General, 1999-2000
    - Biotechnology and Food, 1999-2000
  - Audio/Visual Material, undated, 1991-1999 (Box 89)
    - Unlabeled Cassettes (5), undated
    - Gejdenson on Bryer Cassette (1), 1997
    - Edward Munster Cassette (1), 1999
    - Conference Cassettes (2), undated
    - Public Service Announcement (1), 1999
    - "Keeping America's Dreams Alive" (1), 1996
    - Unlabeled Videocassettes (5), undated
    - Hearings and Floor Statements, Videocassettes (6), 1993-1998
    - Pension Roundtable Videocassettes (2), 1991
    - Veterans' Concerns Videocassette (1), 1999
    - "Your Government and You" Videocassettes (3), undated
    - Event Videocassettes, Dodd Center Opening (3), 1995-1998
    - News and Talk Shows Videocassettes (18), 1992-1996
  - Heritage Corridor, undated, 1992-2000 (Box 90)
    - Press and Letters, undated, 1999-2000
    - Draft Legislation, 1999
    - Faxes and Emails, 1999-2000
    - Hearings, 1999 June 19
    - Compact Language, undated
    - Request for New Legislation, 1999
    - Letters from John Rowland, 1999
    - Original Legislation, 1999
    - Management Plan, 1997
    - Appropriation Letters, 1998-1999
    - Events, 1999
    - Letters of Support, 1999
    - Funding, 1995-1998
    - Floor Statement, 1999 September 13
    - Testimony, 1999-2000
    - House Resolution 1619, 1999
    - Reports to Congress, 1999
    - Heritage Corridor, 1993-1998
    - National Park Service, Final Report, 1993
    - Clippings and Releases, 1993-1995
    - Final Passage, 1993
    - Senate, 1993-1994
    - Babbit's Visit, 1992-1993
    - Reports and Brochures, 1991-1993
    - General files, 1993-1998
  - Transportation, undated, 1993-2000 (Box 91)
    - Tilcon, 2000
    - The Nianric Bay Overlook, 1994-1996
    - East Lyme Broadwalk, 1995-1996
    - Route 195, 1995-1996
    - Southeastern Connecticut Corridor Study, 1999
    - Surface Transportation Board, 1999
    - Transportation Equity Act, TEA 21, 1999-2000
    - Transportation Grant, 1999
    - House Resolution 5164, Tread, 2000
    - Route 2, 1996-1999
    - Quod Gate Amtrak, 1993-1999
    - New London Vista Walkway, 1999
    - Fisher's Island, 1998
    - Groton International Airport, 1998
    - Millenium Trail, 1996-1999
    - Mystic Transportation Equity Act (TEA-21) Problems, 1998-1999
    - Cross Sound Pedestrian Bridge, 1996, 2000
    - Local Ferry Service Study, undated
    - Cross Sound Ferry, 1997-1998
    - Coast Guard Research and Development Center, 1995-1998
    - Coast Guard, 1999-2000
    - China Flights, 2000
    - Amtrak, 1993-2000
    - Amtrak Crossing, 1993-1994, 1997
    - Airplanes, 1999-2000
  - Daily Schedule, 1992 December 9 - 2000 November 7 (Box 92)
    - Gejdenson's Daily Schedule, 1992 December 9- 2000 November 7
  - Speeches, Press Releases, and Mailings, undated, 1981-1984 (Box 93)
    - PCB Oil/Navy, 1981, 1984
    - Gejdenson's Profile, 1981-1982
    - "Cost of Indifference,", 1981
    - New London Town Meeting Card, undated
    - Windham Town Meeting Card, undated
    - Social Security Mailing, 1981 September
    - Questionnaire, undated
    - Nuclear Waste Mailing, 1981 November
    - Mailing Standards, 1981
    - June Mailing, 1981 June
    - Tolland "Dear Friend" Mailing, 1981 September 2
    - Tolland Town Meeting Card, 1981 September